Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
You
أنت
Who are you, really?
من أنت حقا؟
Brother
أخ
I heard things have been dangerous around Qinning Mountain lately.
سمعت أن الأمور أصبحت خطيرة حول جبل تشينينج في الآونة الأخيرة.
Let's take a break.
دعونا نأخذ استراحة.
Then leave as soon as we can.
ثم نغادر في أقرب وقت ممكن.
We better not run into those monsters.
من الأفضل أن لا نواجه هؤلاء الوحوش.
Bah, what bad luck.
آه، ما هذا الحظ السيئ.
I've traveled all over for years.
لقد سافرت إلى كل مكان لسنوات.
Never heard of anything like Rotten Ones.
لم أسمع أبدًا عن شيء مثل Rotten Ones.
Those monsters are so rotten,
تلك الوحوش فاسدة جدًا،
yet they can still attack people.
ومع ذلك فإنهم ما زالوا قادرين على مهاجمة الناس.
Don't say that at night.
لا تقول ذلك في الليل.
Or they'll come for you.
أو أنهم سيأتون إليك.
It's not that creepy.
إنه ليس مخيفا إلى هذه الدرجة.
Th-this...
ث-هذا...
Miss, slow down when you eat.
آنسة، أبطئي عندما تأكلين.
Don't choke.
لا تختنق.
Yeah, miss.
نعم يا آنسة.
People can scare others to death.
يمكن للناس أن يخيفوا الآخرين حتى الموت.
Especially looking like you do.
خاصة أنني أبدو مثلك.
Sir, I didn't mean to.
سيدي، لم أقصد ذلك.
I was just too hungry.
لقد كنت جائعًا جدًا.
We've got plenty of food.
لقد حصلنا على الكثير من الطعام.
We can give it all to you.
يمكننا أن نعطيك كل ذلك.
But you have to do as we say.
ولكن عليك أن تفعل كما نقول.
Let us brothers take good care of you.
دعونا نحن الإخوة نعتني بك جيدًا.
Miss
يفتقد
Why are you running?
لماذا تركض؟
Let us brothers take good care of you.
دعونا نحن الإخوة نعتني بك جيدًا.
There's no one around for miles.
لا يوجد أحد حولنا لعدة أميال.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
It's just the two of us left.
لقد بقينا فقط اثنان.
Hurry, chase her!
اسرع، طاردها!
Brother
أخ
We should get out of here.
ينبغي علينا الخروج من هنا.
This place gives me the creeps.
هذا المكان يجعلني أشعر بالقشعريرة.
No way.
مستحيل.
I haven't had any fun in half a year.
لم أستمتع بأي شيء منذ نصف عام.
I'm not letting this chance slip away.
لن أدع هذه الفرصة تفوتني.
You ate my food,
لقد أكلت طعامي،
so now you belong to me.
الآن أصبحت ملكي.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Let's see where you run now.
دعونا نرى أين تركض الآن.
And then?
وثم؟
I heard those two
سمعت هذين الاثنين
were bitten to death.
لقد تم عضهم حتى الموت.
They say the Rotten Ones
يقولون الفاسدون
start rotting from the belly.
يبدأ بالتعفن من البطن.
When they're dressed,
عندما يرتدون ملابسهم،
you can't tell just by their faces.
لا يمكنك معرفة ذلك من خلال وجوههم فقط.
Who knows,
من يعلم؟
they might be hiding among us.
ربما يكونون مختبئين بيننا.
It's just that we
إنه فقط أننا
haven't noticed.
لم ألاحظ.
Sorry to intrude.
عذرا للتطفل.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
And who are you?
ومن انت؟
We are...
نحن...
We're outsiders.
نحن غرباء.
May I ask,
هل يجوز لي أن أسأل؟
why are you all up so late?
لماذا أنتم مستيقظين حتى وقت متأخر؟
Gathered here like this?
متجمعين هنا مثل هذا؟
What's the occasion?
ما هي المناسبة؟
An occasion?
مناسبة ؟
This is a major event.
هذا حدث كبير.
It's Xuancheng's Fire Sacrifice Festival, held every three years.
إنه مهرجان التضحية بالنار في شيوانتشنغ، والذي يقام كل ثلاث سنوات.
We parade the gods and hold rituals.
نحن نستعرض الآلهة ونقيم الطقوس.
Praying to the Fire God for peace all year.
الصلاة إلى إله النار من أجل السلام طوال العام.
And a bountiful harvest.
وحصاد وفير.
Senior brother
الأخ الأكبر
You really owe me a thank you.
أنت حقا مدين لي بالشكر.
I'm the top fighter of Yun Yin.
أنا المقاتل الأفضل في يون ين.
If I hadn't arrived in time,
لو لم أصل في الوقت المناسب،
and dug you out of that pit,
وأخرجوك من تلك الحفرة،
you wouldn't be seeing this now.
لن ترى هذا الآن.
Thanks, I'll treat you to buns later.
شكرًا لك، سأدعوك إلى الكعك لاحقًا.
Thank you, senior brother.
شكرا لك أخي الأكبر.
Master is so unfair.
المعلم غير عادل تماما.
Didn't even bring us to such a fun place.
ولم يأخذونا حتى إلى مثل هذا المكان الممتع.
If you ask me,
إذا سألتني،
Master just doesn't want to leave.
المعلم لا يريد المغادرة.
Here they come!
إنهم يأتون!
The Chosen One to light the fire today
الشخص المختار لإشعال النار اليوم
is the Crown Prince, Nan Zhengqi.
هو ولي العهد نان تشنغكي.
He's Xuancheng's most favored son.
إنه الابن المفضل لشيوانتشنغ.
Who's that sickly one beside him?
من هو ذلك المريض الذي بجانبه؟
He was injured fighting Mocheng.
لقد أصيب أثناء القتال في موتشنغ.
That's the Second Prince, wounded in the leg.
هذا هو الأمير الثاني، مصاب في ساقه.
Nan Zhengci
نان زينجسي
Bumpkin
ريفي
The once legendary brave youth
الشاب الشجاع الأسطوري ذات يوم
has ended up like this.
لقد انتهى الأمر بهذا الشكل.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
Such a shame.
هذا عار.
The auspicious hour has come.
لقد حانت الساعة الميمونة.
The fire is lit.
تم إشعال النار.
May the weather be favorable.
أتمنى أن يكون الطقس مناسبا.
May all the people be safe.
نرجو السلامة لجميع الناس.
What are they doing?
ماذا يفعلون؟
The royal heirs offer their blood as a sacrifice.
يقدم الورثة الملكيون دمائهم كتضحية.
To show their sincerity.
لإظهار صدقهم.
Praying for the gods to bless the nation's prosperity.
الصلاة إلى الآلهة لكي يبارك ازدهار الأمة.
Praying for divine protection.
الصلاة من أجل الحماية الإلهية.
Everyone, be careful.
الجميع، كونوا حذرين.
Luobo, help them quickly!
لوبو، ساعدهم بسرعة!
Run! Run! Run!
اركض! اركض! اركض!
Protect the princes!
حماية الأمراء!
Second Prince, what's happening?
الأمير الثاني ماذا يحدث؟
Protect the First Prince!
حماية الأمير الأول!
Zhengci
زينجسي
Zhengci, help me!
Zhengci، ساعدني!
Help!
يساعد!
Close the net.
أغلق الشبكة.
We haven't figured it out yet.
لم نتوصل إلى ذلك بعد.
And you just burned it like that.
وأحرقته للتو بهذه الطريقة.
You look unfamiliar. Who are you?
تبدو غريبًا. من أنت؟
Me?
أنا؟
Take a guess.
خذ تخمينًا.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What's your purpose?
ما هو هدفك؟
With that attitude of yours,
مع هذا الموقف منك،
are you planning to take me down too?
هل تخطط لإسقاطي أيضًا؟
That's exactly my intention.
هذا هو قصدي بالضبط.
Move aside! Move aside!
تنحّى جانباً! تنحّى جانباً!
Move! Move! Move!
تحرك! تحرك! تحرك!
Move!
يتحرك!
If you resist again, I won't be so polite.
إذا قاومت مرة أخرى، فلن أكون مهذبًا.
Are you alright? Did you get hurt anywhere?
هل أنت بخير؟ هل تعرضت لأي أذى في أي مكان؟
No.
لا.
Senior brother, are you okay?
أخي الكبير هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine. What about you?
انا بخير. ماذا عنك؟
I'm fine too.
أنا بخير أيضاً.
City Lord, something's wrong!
سيد المدينة، هناك خطأ ما!
The Rotten Ones have appeared again!
لقد ظهر الفاسدون مرة أخرى!
They not only disrupted the Fire Sacrifice Festival,
ولم يكتفوا بتعطيل مهرجان التضحية بالنار،
they almost killed the three young masters.
كادوا أن يقتلوا السادة الشباب الثلاثة.
Rotten Ones?
الفاسدين؟
Like me?
مثلي؟